外国
1972 年，
In 1972,
美国通过了一项具有里程碑意义的
the US passed a landmark
piece of legislation.
美国通过了一项具有里程碑意义的
the US passed a landmark
piece of legislation.
立法，
新法律被称为第九条，
The new law was called Title IX,
它扩大了女性的经济和教育
and it expanded economic
and educational opportunities for women,
它扩大了女性的经济和教育
and it expanded economic
and educational opportunities for women,
机会，尤其是在
especially in higher education.
高等教育领域，
Back then, there was
a 16-percentage-point gap
高等教育领域，
Back then, there was
a 16-percentage-point gap
当时
Back then, there was
a 16-percentage-point gap
在授予男性大学学位方面存在 16 个百分点的差距
in the awarding of college degrees
in favor of men.
在十年内，女性
Within a decade,
women had caught up
and then just blew right past the men.
在十年内，女性
women had caught up
and then just blew right past the men.
赶上了
women had caught up
and then just blew right past the men.
男性，然后又超过了男性。
今天，在授予大学学位方面存在 18 个百分点的差距，
Today, there's an 18-percentage-point gap
in the awarding of college degrees.
今天，在授予大学学位方面存在 18 个百分点的差距，
Today, there's an 18-percentage-point gap
in the awarding of college degrees.
So there's a bigger gender gap today,
因此与
in US higher education,
than there was 50 years ago
when Title IX was passed.
50 年前第九条通过时相比，今天美国高等教育中的性别差距更大
这只是
It's just the other way around.
我以研究不平等为生的另一种方式，在
I study inequality for a living,
and for most of my career,
我以研究不平等为生的另一种方式，在
我职业生涯的大部分时间里，我都专注于
I focused on the divides
of class and race.
我职业生涯的大部分时间里，我都专注于
I focused on the divides
of class and race.
阶级和种族的分歧，
但近年来我
But in recent years,
I've just been noticing
more and more gender gaps
但近年来我
I've just been noticing
more and more gender gaps
注意到越来越多的性别差距，而
and not in the direction
that I was expecting.
注意到越来越多的性别差距，而
and not in the direction
that I was expecting.
不是我原来的方向
and not in the direction
that I was expecting.
期待
可能像你们大多数人一样，我习惯于
Probably like most of you,
I’m used to thinking
about gender equality
可能像你们大多数人一样，我习惯于
I’m used to thinking
about gender equality
考虑性别平等，
and the goal of gender
equality as synonymous
考虑性别平等，
and the goal of gender
equality as synonymous
性别平等的目标是提高
and the goal of gender
equality as synonymous
妇女和女孩地位的代名词，
with the advancement of women and girls.
但现在很明显，有很多
But it's now clear
that there are many boys and men
但现在很明显，有很多
But it's now clear
that there are many boys and men
男孩和男人
But it's now clear
that there are many boys and men
落后了，我们
who've fallen behind
and that we have to be able to think
about gender inequality
落后了，我们
and that we have to be able to think
about gender inequality
必须 能够从两个方向思考性别不平等
and that we have to be able to think
about gender inequality
in both directions.
使这变得困难的一件事是
One thing that makes that hard
is that the changes have been so quick,
使这变得困难的一件事是
One thing that makes that hard
is that the changes have been so quick,
变化如此之快
so rapid,
以至于我们很难更新我们的信念以
that it's hard to update our beliefs
to match the new facts.
以至于我们很难更新我们的信念以
that it's hard to update our beliefs
to match the new facts.
匹配新的事实这有点像
It's a bit like the needles
on a compass swinging round.
匹配新的事实这有点像
It's a bit like the needles
on a compass swinging round.
指南针上的指针
It's a bit like the needles
on a compass swinging round.
突然向北摆动 是南方，南方是
Suddenly north is south
and south is north.
突然向北摆动 是南方，南方是
Suddenly north is south
and south is north.
北方，这确实让人迷失方向，
It's really quite disorienting.
但很明显，至少现在，在某些方面，
But it's clear that on some
measures at least
但很明显，至少现在，在某些方面，
now men are lagging quite a way behind,
男性远远
落后于大学校园，这
not least on college campuses.
And that reflects the fact
that boys are trailing girls
落后于大学校园，这
And that reflects the fact
that boys are trailing girls
反映了这样一个事实，即
And that reflects the fact
that boys are trailing girls
在整个教育
throughout the education system.
系统中，
Two thirds of the top academic
performers in high school,
系统中，
Two thirds of the top academic
performers in high school,
三分之二的男孩都落后于女孩。 根据 GPA
Two thirds of the top academic
performers in high school,
衡量，高中学业成绩最好的
measured by GPA, are girls.
是女生，
而三分之二的垫底学生
And two thirds of those
at the bottom are boys.
而三分之二的垫底学生
And two thirds of those
at the bottom are boys.
是男生——
这不仅仅是在美国。如果我们看看
It's not just in the US.
If we look at the 20 most economically
advanced countries in the world,
这不仅仅是在美国。如果我们看看
If we look at the 20 most economically
advanced countries in the world,
世界上经济最发达的 20 个国家，
there's on average
a 13-percentage-point gap
世界上经济最发达的 20 个国家，
there's on average
a 13-percentage-point gap
平均差距为 13 个百分点 拥有大学学位的
in the share of young men and young women
with a college degree,
平均差距为 13 个百分点 拥有大学学位的
in the share of young men and young women
with a college degree,
年轻男性和年轻女性的比例
in the share of young men and young women
with a college degree,
与年轻女性
with young women much more likely
to have a college degree.
与年轻女性
with young women much more likely
to have a college degree.
更有可能拥有大学学位，
And in some nations,
the gap is much bigger.
更有可能拥有大学学位，
And in some nations,
the gap is much bigger.
在某些国家，挪威的差距要大得多，
例如，
In Norway, for example,
几乎有 20 个百分点，
there's almost a 20-point gap.
就像在美国一样，这些
And just like in the US,
these differences at the college level
就像在美国一样，这些
差异 在大学阶段，反映了
reflect what's happening
earlier in the school system.
差异 在大学阶段，反映了
reflect what's happening
earlier in the school system.
学校系统早期发生的事情，
reflect what's happening
earlier in the school system.
过去可能是男孩
It used to be that maybe boys
were ahead in math and science,
过去可能是男孩
It used to be that maybe boys
were ahead in math and science,
在数学和科学方面领先，女孩
girls were ahead in reading and language
in roughly equal measure.
在数学和科学方面领先，女孩
girls were ahead in reading and language
in roughly equal measure.
在阅读和语言方面的领先程度大致相等，
girls were ahead in reading and language
in roughly equal measure.
这在当今国际上是不正确的，
That's not true today.
在 15 岁时有
Internationally, at the age of 15,
there's a five-point gap
in favor of boys and math.
在 15 岁时有
there's a five-point gap
in favor of boys and math.
五个 - 分数差距有利于男孩在
there's a five-point gap
in favor of boys and math.
数学方面基本上没有差距在
There's essentially no gap in science,
科学方面有轻微差距
a slight gap in favor of girls
actually in science.
科学方面有轻微差距
a slight gap in favor of girls
actually in science.
实际上在科学方面有利于女孩
但男孩
But boys are 30 points
behind girls at the age of 15
但男孩
But boys are 30 points
behind girls at the age of 15
在阅读和语言技能方面比 15 岁的女孩落后 30 分
in reading and language skills.
但并非所有男孩和男人都
But not all boys and men
are struggling in the same way.
但并非所有男孩和男人都
But not all boys and men
are struggling in the same way.
在努力 同样，
The intersection of gender with class
and race really matters here.
在努力 同样，
The intersection of gender with class
and race really matters here.
性别与阶级和种族的交集
The intersection of gender with class
and race really matters here.
在这里确实很重要，因此来自贫困
So boys from poorer households
家庭和中产阶级
and middle-class households,
家庭的男孩上大学的可能性远低于来自
much less likely to attend college
than girls from the same background.
家庭的男孩上大学的可能性远低于来自
much less likely to attend college
than girls from the same background.
相同背景的女孩，
much less likely to attend college
than girls from the same background.
但经济阶梯顶端的差距要小得多
But there's a much smaller gap
at the top of the economic ladder.
但经济阶梯顶端的差距要小得多
But there's a much smaller gap
at the top of the economic ladder.
认为精英
I think one of the reasons
that elites can sometimes struggle
to grasp what's going on with boys and men
认为精英
that elites can sometimes struggle
to grasp what's going on with boys and men
有时难以理解
that elites can sometimes struggle
to grasp what's going on with boys and men
男孩和男人正在发生的事情的原因之一是，
is that the gender gaps
are just much less stark
男孩和男人正在发生的事情的原因之一是，
is that the gender gaps
are just much less stark
在富裕社区中，性别差距要小得多，
in affluent communities.
而对于美国黑人来说，性别差距甚至更大，
And the gender gaps are even
more stark for Black Americans.
而对于美国黑人来说，性别差距甚至更大，
And the gender gaps are even
more stark for Black Americans.
For every Black man
getting a college degree,
因为每个黑人都得到了 大学
For every Black man
getting a college degree,
学位有两个黑人女性，
there are two Black women.
So anybody who really cares
about boys and men
学位有两个黑人女性，
So anybody who really cares
about boys and men
所以任何真正关心男孩
So anybody who really cares
about boys and men
和男人的人都
has to care about racial injustice
and economic inequality.
和男人的人都
has to care about racial injustice
and economic inequality.
必须关心种族不公正和
has to care about racial injustice
and economic inequality.
经济不平等，
任何真正关心
And anybody who really cares
about racial injustice
任何真正关心
And anybody who really cares
about racial injustice
种族不公正和经济不平等的人都
and economic inequality
必须关心男孩和男人，
has to care about boys and men.
因为教育系统
Now, the fact that the education system
doesn't seem to be working very well
因为教育系统
Now, the fact that the education system
doesn't seem to be working very well
似乎对
for lots of boys and men
很多男孩和男人来说效果不是很好 显然不是
is obviously not intentional.
故意的
There wasn't a feminist
conspiracy 100 years ago
一百年前没有女权主义阴谋说
There wasn't a feminist
conspiracy 100 years ago
好可能需要一个世纪但
to say, "Well, it might take a century,
but eventually we'll overtake them."
好可能需要一个世纪但
to say, "Well, it might take a century,
but eventually we'll overtake them."
最终我们会超越他们
(Laughter)
Especially as it was men
who mostly designed the school system.
最终我们会超越他们
Especially as it was men
who mostly designed the school system.
特别是 因为主要是男性
Especially as it was men
who mostly designed the school system.
设计了学校系统，所以
What’s happened is that
as the artificial and sexist barriers
设计了学校系统，所以
What’s happened is that
as the artificial and sexist barriers
发生的事情是，随着
What’s happened is that
as the artificial and sexist barriers
that were placed in front
of women and girls
摆在妇女和女孩面前的人为和性别歧视的障碍
have been successively removed,
相继被移除，因此
so their natural advantages
in the classroom have been revealed.
相继被移除，因此
so their natural advantages
in the classroom have been revealed.
Compared to girls,
与女孩相比，她们在课堂上的天然优势已经显露出来男孩面临两大挑战
boys face two big structural
disadvantages in education.
与女孩相比，她们在课堂上的天然优势已经显露出来男孩面临两大挑战
boys face two big structural
disadvantages in education.
教育中的结构性劣势
boys face two big structural
disadvantages in education.
首先，
First, their brains simply develop later.
他们的大脑只是后来发展
计划组织和
The skills of planning, organization
and impulse control
计划组织和
The skills of planning, organization
and impulse control
冲动控制的技能与前
are associated with the prefrontal cortex,
额叶皮层有关，前额叶皮层在
which develops in adolescence especially.
青春期发育，尤其是但
But about a year later, on average,
for boys than for girls.
青春期发育，尤其是但
But about a year later, on average,
for boys than for girls.
男孩平均比女孩晚一年左右，
所以
So there's a significant difference there
in the timing of brain development.
所以
So there's a significant difference there
in the timing of brain development.
在时间上存在显着差异 大脑发育
社会科学家将那些技能
Social scientists refer to those skills,
planning, organization, etcetera,
社会科学家将那些技能
Social scientists refer to those skills,
planning, organization, etcetera,
规划组织等称为
as non-cognitive skills.
非认知技能
我喜欢将它们视为化学
I like to think of them
as "chemistry homework" skills.
我喜欢将它们视为化学
I like to think of them
as "chemistry homework" skills.
作业技能
你知道做你的化学作业
You know, doing your chemistry homework
requires a lot of steps.
你知道做你的化学作业
You know, doing your chemistry homework
requires a lot of steps.
需要很多步骤
你必须在课堂上集中注意力
You have to be paying attention in class
when the assignment is given.
你必须在课堂上集中注意力
You have to be paying attention in class
when the assignment is given.
当作业是 如果你必须
You have to make a note of it.
记下来，你必须在几个
You have to remember hours later
that you're supposed to do it.
记下来，你必须在几个
You have to remember hours later
that you're supposed to do it.
小时后记住你应该做的
You have to remember hours later
that you're supposed to do it.
你必须真正坐下来做，而
You have to actually sit down and do it,
instead of something
more enticing instead.
你必须真正坐下来做，而
instead of something
more enticing instead.
不是做一些更诱人的事情，
instead of something
more enticing instead.
记住这是化学
And remember, it's chemistry homework,
so that's everything.
记住这是化学
And remember, it's chemistry homework,
so that's everything.
作业，所以这就是
(Laughter)
我所知道的一切抱歉 这里有一些化学家，
Sorry, I know there are some
chemists here, I'm sorry.
我所知道的一切抱歉 这里有一些化学家，
Sorry, I know there are some
chemists here, I'm sorry.
对不起，
Sorry, I know there are some
chemists here, I'm sorry.
然后把它转过来，
And then turn it in.
这是正确的很多步骤，
That's a lot of steps, right?
That's a lot.
这是正确的很多步骤，
完成作业的法律要求你的
Getting your homework done
requires your impulse control
完成作业的法律要求你的
Getting your homework done
requires your impulse control
冲动控制与
to match what psychologists refer to
as sensation seeking.
冲动控制与
to match what psychologists refer to
as sensation seeking.
心理学家所说的感觉
to match what psychologists refer to
as sensation seeking.
寻求相匹配，基本上是想要去做
Basically, that urge to go and do
something more fun, more exciting.
寻求相匹配，基本上是想要去做
Basically, that urge to go and do
something more fun, more exciting.
更有趣的事情的冲动 令人兴奋
，甚至在青春期最困难的时期，也是
And even in the most difficult
years of adolescence,
，甚至在青春期最困难的时期，也是
And even in the most difficult
years of adolescence,
which are also the crucial years
for educational success,
教育成功的关键时期，
which are also the crucial years
for educational success,
女孩在
girls have a reasonable balance between
impulse control and sensation seeking.
女孩在
girls have a reasonable balance between
impulse control and sensation seeking.
冲动控制和寻求感觉之间保持合理的平衡，
girls have a reasonable balance between
impulse control and sensation seeking.
但对于青春期男孩来说，这是一个非常不同的故事，
But it's a very different story
for adolescent boys.
但对于青春期男孩来说，这是一个非常不同的故事，
But it's a very different story
for adolescent boys.
他们有更高水平
They have higher levels
of sensation seeking.
他们有更高水平
They have higher levels
of sensation seeking.
的感觉寻求，并且更少
And with that less developed
prefrontal cortex,
的感觉寻求，并且更少
And with that less developed
prefrontal cortex,
发达的前额叶皮层
they have significantly lower levels
of impulse control.
Again, on average.
Now if you still don't believe me,
如果你仍然不相信我的话，他们现在的冲动控制水平平均再次显着
go into any ninth or 10th grade classroom
降低
and ask all the students
to open up their backpacks.
降低
and ask all the students
to open up their backpacks.
(Laughter)
Most, many, at least of the girls,
will have pretty carefully organized,
精心组织并贴上标签
nicely labeled binders.
的活页夹
，对于许多（如果不是大多数）男孩来说，这就像
And for many, if not most of the boys,
it will resemble a small,
controlled explosion.
，对于许多（如果不是大多数）男孩来说，这就像
it will resemble a small,
controlled explosion.
一个小型受控
it will resemble a small,
controlled explosion.
爆炸。
(Laughter)
It's not that girls are smarter than boys.
这并不是说女孩比男孩更聪明，
There's no gender gap
in intelligence levels
在任何一个方向的智力水平上都没有性别差距，
in either direction.
只是女孩发展出更多
It is just that girls develop more
of these non-cognitive skills,
只是女孩发展出更多
It is just that girls develop more
of these non-cognitive skills,
这些非- 认知技能 这些
these "chemistry homework" skills,
化学作业技能
somewhat earlier than boys do.
比男孩早一些
这只是一个事实
That's just a fact.
但我们在教育政策中忽略了一个事实
But it is a fact that we ignore
in education policy.
但我们在教育政策中忽略了一个事实
But it is a fact that we ignore
in education policy.
The second big structural problem
that boys face in the classroom
is the lack of male teachers.
After falling for decades,
the share of K-12 teachers who are male
in the US is now just 23 percent.
-12 在美国，男性教师
the share of K-12 teachers who are male
in the US is now just 23 percent.
现在只有 23%，
And falling.
而且男性教师的缺乏
And the lack of male teachers matters
for at least three reasons.
而且男性教师的缺乏
And the lack of male teachers matters
for at least three reasons.
至少有三个原因很重要，首先，
First, for many children, [they]
can be an important male role model,
至少有三个原因很重要，首先，
First, for many children, [they]
can be an important male role model,
对于许多孩子来说，如果他们尤其是没有男性的话，可能会成为一个重要的
First, for many children, [they]
can be an important male role model,
男性榜样
especially if they don't have one at home.
在
家里和第二个男老师似乎
And second, male teachers
appear to be more sensitive
家里和第二个男老师似乎
And second, male teachers
appear to be more sensitive
to the specific challenges
of boys in the classroom.
对课堂上男孩的具体挑战更敏感
to the specific challenges
of boys in the classroom.
我能清楚地记得我自己的
I can vividly remember my own experience.
经历
I can actually still feel what it was like
to sit for what felt like hours on end
经历
I can actually still feel what it was like
to sit for what felt like hours on end
硬塑料椅子，
on an incredibly hard plastic chair,
and that it was actually a male
primary school teacher, Mr. Cole,
硬塑料椅子，
and that it was actually a male
primary school teacher, Mr. Cole,
实际上是一位男
and that it was actually a male
primary school teacher, Mr. Cole,
小学老师科尔先生给了我们更多的
who gave us more opportunities
to move around,
小学老师科尔先生给了我们更多的
who gave us more opportunities
to move around,
活动机会，让
made the lessons a little
bit more interactive.
活动机会，让
made the lessons a little
bit more interactive.
课程更具互动性，
男老师可能很重要的第三个原因
And the third reason
male teachers may matter
男老师可能很重要的第三个原因
And the third reason
male teachers may matter
是有一些证据表明，
is there's some evidence that,
especially in subjects like English,
是有一些证据表明，
尤其是在英语等科目中
是男孩们远远落后的地方
which is where the boys
have fallen so far behind,
是男孩们远远落后的地方
which is where the boys
have fallen so far behind,
有一个男老师似乎
having a male teacher
seems to dispel the idea
有一个男老师似乎
having a male teacher
seems to dispel the idea
打消了阅读和
that reading and writing
just aren't for me or for people like me.
打消了阅读和
that reading and writing
just aren't for me or for people like me.
写作不适合我或像
that reading and writing
just aren't for me or for people like me.
我这样的人的想法，就像有一个
In a similar way to how
having a female teacher
我这样的人的想法，就像有一个
In a similar way to how
having a female teacher
女老师在历史上帮助
has historically helped girls
in STEM subjects.
女老师在历史上帮助
has historically helped girls
in STEM subjects.
女孩学习干科一样
现在在我们太多的学校里，
Right now, in too many of our schools,
我们的男孩感觉就像方钉被
our boys feel like square pegs
being forced into round holes.
我们的男孩感觉就像方钉被
our boys feel like square pegs
being forced into round holes.
强行塞进圆孔里，
And too often our response
is to try and fix the boys
强行塞进圆孔里，
And too often our response
is to try and fix the boys
我们的反应往往是试图
And too often our response
is to try and fix the boys
修复男孩
And too often our response
is to try and fix the boys
而不是修复学校
rather than fix the schools.
The problems of boys are turned
into problems with boys.
如果他们努力解决问题，男孩的问题就会变成男孩的问题 静坐或集中
If they struggle to sit still
or pay attention
如果他们努力解决问题，男孩的问题就会变成男孩的问题 静坐或集中
If they struggle to sit still
or pay attention
注意力或专注于一项任务
or apply themselves to a task,
他们可能被诊断出患有某种
they may be diagnosed
with some kind of disability.
他们可能被诊断出患有某种
they may be diagnosed
with some kind of disability.
残疾 他们的问题因此
Their problems are thus medicalized
and often medicated.
残疾 他们的问题因此
Their problems are thus medicalized
and often medicated.
在当今美国被医学化并经常接受药物治疗 23% 的学龄
In the US today, 23 percent
of school-age boys
在当今美国被医学化并经常接受药物治疗 23% 的学龄
In the US today, 23 percent
of school-age boys
男孩被诊断​​出患有某种形式
have been diagnosed with some form
of developmental disability.
男孩被诊断​​出患有某种形式
have been diagnosed with some form
of developmental disability.
的发育障碍
Twice the rate for girls.
正如你所料，女孩多动症的比率是最
ADHD, as you might expect,
is the most common.
正如你所料，女孩多动症的比率是最
ADHD, as you might expect,
is the most common.
常见的，
但实际上，
But really,
当我们四分之一的男孩
when one in four of our boys
has a developmental disability,
当我们四分之一的男孩
when one in four of our boys
has a developmental disability,
有发育障碍时，
when one in four of our boys
has a developmental disability,
我似乎很清楚，是
it seems clear to me
that it is the system which is disabling
我似乎很清楚，是
it seems clear to me
that it is the system which is disabling
系统而
it seems clear to me
that it is the system which is disabling
不是残疾的男孩
rather than the boys who are disabled.
(Applause)
不是残疾的男孩
现在有很多我们 为了让
Now, there's a lot we can do
to make the education system
work better for boys.
现在有很多我们 为了让
to make the education system
work better for boys.
教育系统更好地为男孩服务，我们可以做些什么让我们从
Let's start with those two big problems,
大脑后期发育和缺乏
of later brain development
and lack of male teachers.
大脑后期发育和缺乏
of later brain development
and lack of male teachers.
男教师这两个大问题开始，所以首先我们应该在
So first, we should start
boys in school a year later.
男教师这两个大问题开始，所以首先我们应该在
So first, we should start
boys in school a year later.
一年后让男孩上学，考虑到这些问题，我们的
想法是创造公平的
And the idea there
is to level the playing field,
想法是创造公平的
And the idea there
is to level the playing field,
竞争环境
given those differences
in the timing of brain development.
竞争环境
given those differences
in the timing of brain development.
大脑发育时间的差异
And actually that's already
quite common practice
大脑发育时间的差异
And actually that's already
quite common practice
实际上这在
And actually that's already
quite common practice
私立学校和许多
at private schools and in lots
of affluent communities,
私立学校和许多
at private schools and in lots
of affluent communities,
富裕社区已经很普遍但
but it's actually not the boys
from rich families
富裕社区已经很普遍但
but it's actually not the boys
from rich families
实际上并不是来自富裕家庭的男孩
but it's actually not the boys
from rich families
将从额外的一年中受益最多而是
who will benefit the most
from that extra year.
将从额外的一年中受益最多而是
who will benefit the most
from that extra year.
来自低收入
It's the boys from lower-income,
贫困社区和家庭的男孩 谁
poorer neighborhoods and families
who would most benefit from the gift
of extra time for development.
贫困社区和家庭的男孩 谁
who would most benefit from the gift
of extra time for development.
最能从额外的
who would most benefit from the gift
of extra time for development.
发展时间中受益，这就是
And that's why I think this should be
a question of public policy.
发展时间中受益，这就是
And that's why I think this should be
a question of public policy.
为什么我认为这应该是一个公共政策问题
And that's why I think this should be
a question of public policy.
Second, we need to recruit hundreds
of thousands more male teachers,
其次，我们需要再招募数十
Second, we need to recruit hundreds
of thousands more male teachers,
万名男教师，尤其是
especially in subjects like English,
在像英语这样的男孩们
where the boys are struggling so much
非常挣扎的科目中 是
and which is the subject
men are least likely to be teaching.
非常挣扎的科目中 是
and which is the subject
men are least likely to be teaching.
男性最不可能教授的学科
and which is the subject
men are least likely to be teaching.
，在这里我认为我们可以
And here I think we can draw
some really good lessons
，在这里我认为我们可以
And here I think we can draw
some really good lessons
从成功的运动中吸取一些非常好的教训，
from the successful movement
让更多的女性和女孩
to get more women and girls
interested in STEM subjects.
让更多的女性和女孩
to get more women and girls
interested in STEM subjects.
对 stem 学科感兴趣，这
So that means setting clear targets,
launching public campaigns
对 stem 学科感兴趣，这
So that means setting clear targets,
launching public campaigns
意味着设定明确的目标，开展
So that means setting clear targets,
launching public campaigns
公共活动
and offering financial scholarships
并为男性提供经济奖学金
to men who want to enter
teaching as a profession.
并为男性提供经济奖学金
to men who want to enter
teaching as a profession.
谁想以教学为
to men who want to enter
teaching as a profession.
职业
Of course, those are changes
that will take time.
职业
Of course, those are changes
that will take time.
当然这些都是
Of course, those are changes
that will take time.
需要时间的变化那些是长期的变化
Those are long-term changes.
And there are millions of boys
and men who are struggling right now.
现在有数以百万计的男孩和男人正在挣扎
所以如果你是父母或老师
And so if you're a parent or a teacher
working with a boy or a young man
所以如果你是父母或老师
And so if you're a parent or a teacher
working with a boy or a young man
工作 和一个现在遇到困难的男孩或年轻人一起，
who's in difficulty right now,
我要给
my message to you is, first,
你的信息是，首先
要小心，即使
be careful not to even inadvertently
judge him against a female standard
要小心，即使
be careful not to even inadvertently
judge him against a female standard
他
or blame him if he's
struggling in a system
他
or blame him if he's
struggling in a system
在一个可能不太适合他的系统中挣扎，也不要无意中根据女性标准判断他或责怪
or blame him if he's
struggling in a system
that just might not be working
very well for him.
他认识到 并尊重
Recognize and respect the ways
in which he's different.
他认识到 并尊重
Recognize and respect the ways
in which he's different.
他与众不同的方式
不要说
Don't say,
为什么你不能更像你的妹妹
"Why can't you be more like your sister?"
甚至不要认为
Try not to even think that.
我们不对待
It's very important
that we don't treat our boys
我们不对待
It's very important
that we don't treat our boys
我们的男孩就像他们是故障
as if they were malfunctioning girls.
女孩一样对待是非常重要的
第二条信息 那些人
And the second message to those people,
cousins, parents, neighbors, friends,
第二条信息 那些人
And the second message to those people,
cousins, parents, neighbors, friends,
表亲父母邻居朋友叔叔
uncles, coaches, anybody
working with a boy or a young man
表亲父母邻居朋友叔叔
uncles, coaches, anybody
working with a boy or a young man
教练任何与现在正在挣扎的男孩或年轻人一起工作的
uncles, coaches, anybody
working with a boy or a young man
人
who is struggling right now,
is simply, thank you.
人
who is struggling right now,
is simply, thank you.
只是谢谢你
Thank you.
他们确实需要你
They do need you.
Of course,
当然
为男孩和男人做更多并不意味着
doing more for boys and men
doesn't mean doing any less
for women and girls.
为男孩和男人做更多并不意味着
doesn't mean doing any less
for women and girls.
为女人和女孩做的更少
对，这就像对
That’s like saying to the parent
of a son and daughter:
对，这就像对
That’s like saying to the parent
of a son and daughter:
一个儿子和女儿的父母说，你
"You're only allowed to care
about one of them."
一个儿子和女儿的父母说，你
"You're only allowed to care
about one of them."
只能关心他们中的一个，
这是一种零和思维，
And it's the kind of zero-sum thinking
对我们的政治和文化造成了如此大的损害，
that is doing so much damage
to our politics and to our culture.
对我们的政治和文化造成了如此大的损害，
that is doing so much damage
to our politics and to our culture.
我们可以考虑
We can think two thoughts at once.
两种想法 曾经我们可以同时做两
We can do two things at once.
件事 一次有两种
(Applause)
想法 一次有两件事
Two thoughts at once, two things at once.
That's why Norway,
想法 一次有两件事
这就是为什么挪威
That's why Norway,
这个国家
a country that's made huge investments,
为妇女和女孩做出了相当正确的巨额投资，但
quite rightly for women and girls,
现在男孩和男人
but where boys and men have now fallen
behind on many measures,
现在男孩和男人
but where boys and men have now fallen
behind on many measures,
在许多措施上落后了，它发起了一个
has launched a commission
for boys and men.
在许多措施上落后了，它发起了一个
has launched a commission
for boys and men.
男孩委员会， 男人们，
我今天谈到了教育，
I've talked about education today,
但还有许多其他领域，
but there are many other areas
where many boys and men are struggling,
但还有许多其他领域，
but there are many other areas
where many boys and men are struggling,
许多男孩和男人正在苦苦挣扎，
but there are many other areas
where many boys and men are struggling,
包括心理健康，包括
including in mental health,
including suicide risk.
包括心理健康，包括
including in mental health,
including suicide risk.
自杀风险、
孤独感和家庭生活
Loneliness and belonging,
family life, employment.
孤独感和家庭生活
就业归属感
，我认为
And I don't think we can afford
to get this wrong.
，我认为
And I don't think we can afford
to get this wrong.
如果有的话，我们不能犯错 社会中的真正问题
If there are real problems in a society,
，负责任的人不承认
and responsible people
don't acknowledge and address them,
，负责任的人不承认
and responsible people
don't acknowledge and address them,
和解决这些问题，
and responsible people
don't acknowledge and address them,
不负责任的人会利用它们，
irresponsible people will exploit them.
并且在网上和投票箱上已经在这个问题上发生了，
And that is already
happening on this issue,
并且在网上和投票箱上已经在这个问题上发生了，
And that is already
happening on this issue,
both online and at the ballot box.
我们不能通过
We cannot leave a vacuum
by neglecting this issue.
我们不能通过
We cannot leave a vacuum
by neglecting this issue.
忽视这个问题来留下真空，
未来不能是女性，
The future cannot be female.
也不能 当然，
Nor, of course, can the future be male.
未来可以是男性吗？
未来必须属于
The future has to be for every single
one of us, every boy and girl,
未来必须属于
The future has to be for every single
one of us, every boy and girl,
我们每个人，每个男孩和女孩，我们必须
we have to rise together.
一起成长谢谢谢谢谢谢
Thank you.
(Applause)
(Applause ends)
理查德谢谢你我有一个
Chris Anderson: Thank you, Richard.
I've got a question for you.
理查德谢谢你我有一个
顾客好吧过来这边
Come this way.
看看你 在那里
So you gave great advice there
for the system as a whole,
看看你 在那里
So you gave great advice there
for the system as a whole,
为整个系统为教师
for teachers, for parents.
为父母提供了很好的建议但是假设你是一个 14
But suppose you're a 14-year-old boy
listening to this talk.
为父母提供了很好的建议但是假设你是一个 14
But suppose you're a 14-year-old boy
listening to this talk.
岁的男孩听这个演讲
What would you say to him?
你会对他说什么
Richard Reeves: Huh.
我首先要说的是如果你
Well, the first thing I’d say
is that if you are struggling at school
我首先要说的是如果你
Well, the first thing I’d say
is that if you are struggling at school
在学校挣扎或者 在
Well, the first thing I’d say
is that if you are struggling at school
你生活的某些方面，这几乎
or in some aspects of your life,
that's almost certainly
not just your fault.
你生活的某些方面，这几乎
that's almost certainly
not just your fault.
肯定不仅仅是你的错，也可能是
It may be that the system
is just not working for you.
肯定不仅仅是你的错，也可能是
It may be that the system
is just not working for you.
系统不适合你
It may be that the system
is just not working for you.
我要说的第二件事是
The second thing I would say is ...
我们看到你，我们
We see you.
得到了你，我们明白我们得到了你的
We've got you.
We understand, we've got your back.
得到了你，我们明白我们得到了你的
支持，第三件事我会说 说的是
And the third thing I would say is,
don't follow the people
支持，第三件事我会说 说的是
And the third thing I would say is,
don't follow the people
不要听那些说
who say that the reason you're struggling
is because women are flourishing.
不要听那些说
who say that the reason you're struggling
is because women are flourishing.
你挣扎的原因是因为
who say that the reason you're struggling
is because women are flourishing.
女性正在蓬勃发展或因为
Or because of feminism.
女权主义或因为
Or because of changes in society.
社会变化的人，我们必须以某种方式
That we somehow have to,
in order to lift boys up,
社会变化的人，我们必须以某种方式
提升男孩，我们必须以某种方式推动
we have to somehow push women
and girls back down again.
提升男孩，我们必须以某种方式推动
we have to somehow push women
and girls back down again.
女性和 女孩们再次退缩 不要
Don't fall for that.
因为那个而堕落 明白我们只是
Understand that we get
that you're struggling,
因为那个而堕落 明白我们只是
Understand that we get
that you're struggling,
知道你在挣扎 但不要
but don't turn this into zero-sum.
把它变成零和 不要转向
Don't turn to some of the darker corners
of the internet where unfortunately,
把它变成零和 不要转向
Don't turn to some of the darker corners
of the internet where unfortunately,
互联网的一些更黑暗的角落
Don't turn to some of the darker corners
of the internet where unfortunately,
不幸的是，这就是
that is the message
many of our boys are getting.
不幸的是，这就是
that is the message
many of our boys are getting.
信息 我们的许多男孩都得到了，但
that is the message
many of our boys are getting.
第一部分非常重要，
But the first part
that's really important,
第一部分非常重要，
But the first part
that's really important,
他们说我们
that whole conversation
that we had about belonging,
他们说我们
that whole conversation
that we had about belonging,
关于归属感的整个谈话在归属感方面有很大的不同，
the wonderful difference in belonging,
如果我们的男孩不觉得
if our boys don't feel that they belong,
他们属于我们，
我们已经得到了他们，我们看到了
that we've got them, that we see them,
他们。 我们将更容易受到
they're going to be much more
vulnerable to those voices.
他们。 我们将更容易受到
they're going to be much more
vulnerable to those voices.
这些声音的影响，所以不要听那些
So don't listen to those voices,
but we need them to listen to us instead.
这些声音的影响，所以不要听那些
So don't listen to those voices,
but we need them to listen to us instead.
声音，但我们需要他们听我们的，而不是
So don't listen to those voices,
but we need them to listen to us instead.
非常感谢，再次感谢，
CA: Thank you so much.
谢谢
(Applause)